<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cvs on Aishik Pyne</title><link>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/</link><description>Recent content in Cvs on Aishik Pyne</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://aishikpyne.com/cv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering</title><link>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/jadavpur-university/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/jadavpur-university/</guid><description> Bachelor of Engineering, in Computer Science and Engineering: CGPA 8.3/10 (absolute scale). First Class Honors. Graduate Coursework: Object-Oriented-Programming, Data Structures and Algorithms, Graph Theory, Computer Ar- chitecture, Operating Systems, Linux Shell, DBMS (Relational Model), Networking, Compiler Design.</description></item><item><title>High School</title><link>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/xaviers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/xaviers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Intern - Azure Agriculture Team</title><link>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/microsoft-internship/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/microsoft-internship/</guid><description> Created meta-data index of multi-band satellite images from MODIS and Sentinel to enable geo-spatial queries and lazy processing and deployed it using Azure Data Factory</description></item><item><title>Master's in Computing, Specialization Artificial Intelligence</title><link>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/nus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/nus/</guid><description> Master of Computing, Specializating in Artificial Intelligence: CGPA: 4.7/5 Graduate Coursework: Advanced Topics in Robotics, Intelligent Robots, Trustworthy ML, Uncertainty Modelling in AI, Neural Networks and Deep Learning.</description></item><item><title>Software Engineer II</title><link>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/microsoft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aishikpyne.com/cv/microsoft/</guid><description>Azure Agriculture Data-ScienceTeam(FarmBeats) Segmented crops from satellite imagery using CNNs in an attempt to capture spatial information from remote sensors. AzureBlockchainService(ABS) DevelopedABSPortal Extension to allow customers to Create and ManageABS deployments from AzurePortalUI. Developed Azure Compliant Resource Provider and background TaskExecutionEngine for the reliable asynchronous deployment of Hyperledger-Fabric managed clusters. Designed and orchestrated safe deployment pipelines for global ABS service roll-out. Maintained and supported ABS and Azure Blockchain Workbench as a live-site front-liner to mitigate live customer issues.</description></item></channel></rss>